[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "Which sport do the All Whites play?",
      "answer1": "Netball",
      "answer2": "Rugby",
      "answer3": "Soccer",
      "answer4": "Badminton"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "What type of animal is the kiore, which was brought to NZ by early Polynesian settlers?",
      "answer1": "A cat",
      "answer2": "A rat",
      "answer3": "A bat",
      "answer4": "A bird"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "Which sport do the All Whites play?",
      "answer1": "Netball",
      "answer2": "Rugby",
      "answer3": "Soccer",
      "answer4": "Badminton"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "What is the name for a hot spring that erupts periodically, pushing a column of hot water and steam into the air?",
      "answer1": "A pier",
      "answer2": "A geyser",
      "answer3": "A volcano",
      "answer4": "A boink"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "What is the biggest spectator sport in NZ?",
      "answer1": "Netball",
      "answer2": "Rugby",
      "answer3": "Soccer",
      "answer4": "Cricker"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "New Zealander Ernest Rutherford is famous for splitting what?",
      "answer1": "Hairs",
      "answer2": "Siamese twins",
      "answer3": "The atom",
      "answer4": "DNA"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "Richard Pearse is most famous for his early experiments with what?",
      "answer1": "Flying",
      "answer2": "Swimming",
      "answer3": "Art",
      "answer4": "Diving"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "Which city in the South Island has the most people living in it?",
      "answer1": "Christchurch",
      "answer2": "Picton",
      "answer3": "Queenstown",
      "answer4": "Blenheim"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "Nuclear power generates what percentage of NZ's electricity?",
      "answer1": "None",
      "answer2": "10%",
      "answer3": "20%",
      "answer4": "50%"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "Which one of these is not a native tree?",
      "answer1": "Kauri",
      "answer2": "Pine",
      "answer3": "Totara",
      "answer4": "Rimu"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "Who are Pakeha?",
      "answer1": "Asians",
      "answer2": "Australians",
      "answer3": "Non-maori people",
      "answer4": "New Zealanders"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "What is the common nickname for New Zealanders?",
      "answer1": "Kiwis",
      "answer2": "Rugbys",
      "answer3": "Islanders",
      "answer4": "Kakapeople"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "What is Te Reo Maori?",
      "answer1": "A theme park",
      "answer2": "A waterfall",
      "answer3": "A language",
      "answer4": "A type of bird"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "NZ has had several epidemics. What is an epidemic?",
      "answer1": "A rise in money",
      "answer2": "A disease that spreads quickly",
      "answer3": "A lockdown",
      "answer4": "A change in government"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "In NZ slang, what does it mean to be 'a bit of a dag'?",
      "answer1": "A famous person",
      "answer2": "A mischievous person",
      "answer3": "A comedian",
      "answer4": "A sports player"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "Which sport do the All Whites play?",
      "answer1": "Netball",
      "answer2": "Rugby",
      "answer3": "Soccer",
      "answer4": "Badminton"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "correct-answer": 4,
      "question": "What colour is mawhero?",
      "answer1": "White",
      "answer2": "Red",
      "answer3": "Black",
      "answer4": "Pink"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "What is the social and spiritual centre where Maori meet and celebrate?",
      "answer1": "A marae",
      "answer2": "A whare",
      "answer3": "A school",
      "answer4": "A court"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "Why has no living human ever seen a living moa?",
      "answer1": "Because they are invisible to us",
      "answer2": "Because they are extinct",
      "answer3": "Because they are in outer space",
      "answer4": "Because they run away from us"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "What type of animal is a kaka?",
      "answer1": "A bird",
      "answer2": "A fish",
      "answer3": "A lion",
      "answer4": "A cat"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "What are kowhai, karaka, totara, kauri, and rimu?",
      "answer1": "Colours",
      "answer2": "Native trees",
      "answer3": "Birds",
      "answer4": "Toys"
    }
  ]